J. D. Sloan Photographs MS247
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
J. D. Sloan Photographs
circa 1978 -- 2013
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Sloan, J. D., 1946-
MS247
8.4 Linear Feet
This collection contains photographic prints, negatives, and CDs of digital photographs taken by JD Sloan, documenting university events and campus life between approximately 1978 and 2013.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of J. D. Sloan, and transferred by the Office of the Board of Trustees, 2018, accession MS-2019-004.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged in two chronological series by format: Photographic prints and negatives; and Born digital materials.
Biographical / Historical
J. D. Sloan is an American photographer born in 1946 in Springfield, Massachusetts. From the late 1970s through the mid 2010s, Sloan took photographs documenting university events and campus life at Tufts University.
Sloan's work is held in the collections of the Reva and David Logan Foundation in Chicago, IL; the Carnegie Museum of Art in Pittsburgh, PA; and the Harry Ransom Center in Austin, TX, among others. He is the owner of JD Sloan Photographs.
Custodial History
This collection was sent to the Office of the Board of Trustees in the fall of 2017, and was transferred to DCA in July of 2018.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains photographic prints, negatives, and CDs of digital photographs taken by JD Sloan, documenting university events and campus life between approximately 1978 and 2013. Highlights include speakers and distinguished guests visiting Tufts, annual events such as Commencement and reunions, openings of buildings and facilities on all campuses, portraits of Tufts staff and presidents, and images of day to day campus life.
Tufts University; Boston Campus; Medford Campus; Grafton Campus
- Photographic prints and negatives, 1978 -- 2013; MS247.001; 7.4 Linear Feet
  Conditions Governing Access
  This series is open for research.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged roughly chronologically.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains photographic prints and negatives of photographs taken by JD Sloan, documenting university events and campus life. Highlights include speakers and distinguished guests visiting Tufts, annual events such as Commencement and reunions, openings of buildings and facilities on all campuses, portraits of Tufts staff and presidents, and images of day to day campus life.
  - Tufts 1980-1981, MS247.001.001.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Open for research.
    - Ambassador from the People's Republic of China, 1980-03-30; MS247.001.001.00001.00001 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      General
      3785-1 to 3785-4
      Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy
      negatives (photographic); Medford Campus
    - Chris Doku, 1980; MS247.001.001.00001.00002 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      1933-4
      School of Dental Medicine
      negatives (photographic); Boston Campus
    - Sloan, 1980 -- 1981; MS247.001.001.00001.00003 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      827-1 to 827-6
      negatives (photographic)
    - Queen Sirikit ( Honorary Degree Recipient), 1980; MS247.001.001.00001.00004 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      4267-1 to 4267-4
      School of Arts and Sciences
    - 1071-1 to 1071-9, 1980 -- 1981; MS247.001.001.00001.00005 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      1071-1 to 1071-9
    - Cutting squid, 1980 -- 1981; MS247.001.001.00001.00006 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      1095-1 to 1095-3
    - CB w/Jeep, 1980 -- 1981; MS247.001.001.00001.00007 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      1104-1 to 1104-3
    - 1146-1 to 1146-3, 1980 -- 1981; MS247.001.001.00001.00008 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      1146-1 to 1146-3
    - 1188 solo, 1980 -- 1981; MS247.001.001.00001.00009 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      1188 and 1191-1
    - Sleeping in the gym Fire? Snowstorm?, 1980 -- 1981; MS247.001.001.00001.00010 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      1191-2 to 1191-4
    - 1433-3, 1980 -- 1981; MS247.001.001.00001.00011 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      1433-3
    - 1433-5, 1980 -- 1981; MS247.001.001.00001.00012 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      1433-5
    - 1433-2, 1980 -- 1981; MS247.001.001.00001.00013 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      1433-2
    - 4349-2 to 4349-3, 1980 -- 1981; MS247.001.001.00001.00014 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      4349-2 to 4349-3
    - 4357-5 and 4357-7, 1980 -- 1981; MS247.001.001.00001.00015 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      4357-5 and 4357-7
    - Seymour Simches Class, 1980 -- 1981; MS247.001.001.00001.00016 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      4349-1 and 4357-2 to 4357-4
    - 4374-1 to 4374-2, 1980 -- 1981; MS247.001.001.00001.00017 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      4374-1 to 4374-2
    - 4382-1 to 4382-6, 1980 -- 1981; MS247.001.001.00001.00018 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      4382-1 to 4382-6
    - 4407-1 to 4407-2, 1980 -- 1981; MS247.001.001.00001.00019 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      4407-1 to 4407-2
    - Ballou Hall, 1980 -- 1981; MS247.001.001.00001.00020 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      4407-1
    - Fletcher, 1980 -- 1981; MS247.001.001.00001.00021 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      4408-1 to 4408-2
    - Roche-Fletcher, 1980 -- 1981; MS247.001.001.00001.00022 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      1419-1 to 1419-3
    - 1421-4, 1980 -- 1981; MS247.001.001.00001.00023 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      1421-4
    - Eleanor Massaroti, 1980 -- 1980; MS247.001.001.00001.00024 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      1421-1 to 1421-3
    - Solo Sheet, 1980 -- 1981; MS247.001.001.00001.00025 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      1385
    - 1527-2 and 1528-2 and 1528-3, 1980 -- 1981; MS247.001.001.00001.00026 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      1527-2 and 1528-2 and 1528-3
    - 1939-2, 1980 -- 1981; MS247.001.001.00001.00027 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      1939-2
    - 1939-1, 1980 -- 1981; MS247.001.001.00001.00028 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      1939-1
    - 3302-1 to 3302-13, 1980 -- 1981; MS247.001.001.00001.00029 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      3302-1 to 3302-13
    - Parents, 1980 -- 1981; MS247.001.001.00001.00030 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      4501-1 to 4502-16
    - Jean Francois-Poncet, 1980 -- 1981; MS247.001.001.00001.00031 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      3703-1 to 3703-5
    - Karsh and Single Continuing Ed, 1980 -- 1981; MS247.001.001.00001.00032 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      7254-1 and 7254-2 and 7221
      Cummings School of Veterinary Medicine
      negatives (photographic); Grafton Campus
    - 7329-1 to 7329-5, 1980 -- 1981; MS247.001.001.00001.00033 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      7329-1 to 7329-5
    - 1-10 Vet School, 1980 -- 1981; MS247.001.001.00001.00034 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      7389-1 to 7389-10 ( 7389-2 frame 13 Jeff Erikson)
    - Med Schl Stud Cover & Extra-Mayer Commencement Robes, 1980 -- 1981; MS247.001.001.00001.00035 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      7406 and 7390
    - Tufts Vet, 1980 -- 1981; MS247.001.001.00001.00036 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      1835-1 to 1835-8
    - Solo Cabot Center, 1980 -- 1981; MS247.001.001.00001.00037 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      1797
    - 7499-1 to 7499-5, 1980 -- 1981; MS247.001.001.00001.00038 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      7499-1 to 7499-5
    - Kleine Vet School, 1980 -- 1981; MS247.001.001.00001.00039 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      7451-1 to 7451-3
    - 7462-1 to 7462-10, 1980 -- 1981; MS247.001.001.00001.00040 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      7462-1 to 7462-10
    - 7463-1 to 7462-2, 1980 -- 1981; MS247.001.001.00001.00041 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      7463-1 to 7462-2
    - 7490-1 to 7490-6, 1980 -- 1981; MS247.001.001.00001.00042 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      7490-1 to 7490-6
    - 1771-1 to 1771-2, 1980 -- 1981; MS247.001.001.00001.00043 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      1771-1 to 1771-2
    - 1772-1 to 1772-2, 1980 -- 1981; MS247.001.001.00001.00044 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      1772-1 to 1772-2
    - 1798-1 to 1798-5, 1980 -- 1981; MS247.001.001.00001.00045 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      1798-1 to 1798-5
    - Decision (Rubin), 1980 -- 1981; MS247.001.001.00001.00046 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      7469-1 to 7469-2
    - Susan Kotter / Cat portraits, 1980 -- 1981; MS247.001.001.00001.00047 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      4992-1 to 4992-3
    - Solo Sheet, 1980 -- 1981; MS247.001.001.00001.00048 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      4948 and 4991
    - Mayer Smiling, 1980 -- 1981; MS247.001.001.00001.00049 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      1433-1
    - 4476-2, 1980 -- 1981; MS247.001.001.00001.00050 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      4476-2
  - Very Early Tufts, 1978 -- 1982; MS247.001.001.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Includes opening of Grafton, 81-82 Commencement Fletcher
    - 1982 Commencement, 1978 -- 1982; MS247.001.001.00002.00001 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      5743-1 to 5743-7
    - 1981 Commencement / Fletcher Graduation, 1978 -- 1982; MS247.001.001.00002.00002 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      7161-1 to 7161-11
    - Fletcher, 1978 -- 1982; MS247.001.001.00002.00003 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      5711-1 to 5711-5
    - Opening of Grafton, 1978 -- 1982; MS247.001.001.00002.00004 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      5703-1 to 5703-9
    - Tufts Vet, 1978 -- 1982; MS247.001.001.00002.00005 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      8784-1 to 8784-7
    - Tufts Reunion, 1978 -- 1982; MS247.001.001.00002.00006 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      5736-1 to 5736-4
    - Tufts 1000, 1978 -- 1982; MS247.001.001.00002.00007 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      5454-1 to 5454-2
    - 5455-1 to 5455-4, 1978 -- 1982; MS247.001.001.00002.00008 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      5455-1 to 5455-4
    - 5421-1 to 5421-5, 1978 -- 1982; MS247.001.001.00002.00009 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      5421-1 to 5421-5
    - 5391-1 to 5391-3, 1978 -- 1982; MS247.001.001.00002.00010 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      5391-1 to 5391-3
    - 1527-1, 1978 -- 1982; MS247.001.001.00002.00011 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      1527-1
    - 1528-1 to 1528-2, 1978 -- 1982; MS247.001.001.00002.00012 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      1528-1 to 1528-2
    - 4914-1 to 4914-4, 1978 -- 1982; MS247.001.001.00002.00013 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      4914-1 to 4914-4
    - 5166-1 to 5166-3, 1978 -- 1982; MS247.001.001.00002.00014 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      5166-1 to 5166-3
    - 5108-1 to 5108-2, 1978 -- 1982; MS247.001.001.00002.00015 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      5108-1 to 5108-2
    - 5165-1 to 5165-9, 1978 -- 1982; MS247.001.001.00002.00016 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      5165-1 to 5165-9
    - Tufts Vet, 1978 -- 1982; MS247.001.001.00002.00017 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      4943
    - Vet: 2nd Arthros, 1978 -- 1982; MS247.001.001.00002.00018 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      4944-1 to 4944-5
    - 8938-1 to 8938-4, 1978 -- 1982; MS247.001.001.00002.00019 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      8938-1 to 8938-4
    - Tufts 1000, 1978 -- 1982; MS247.001.001.00002.00020 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      5340-1 to 5340-11
    - 5311-1 to 5311-2, 1978 -- 1982; MS247.001.001.00002.00021 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      5311-1 to 5311-2
    - 5358-1 to 5358-5, 1978 -- 1982; MS247.001.001.00002.00022 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      5358-1 to 5358-5
    - 8937-1 to 8937-2, 1978 -- 1982; MS247.001.001.00002.00023 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      8937-1 to 8937-2
  - Probably #1 Tufts 840102 to 860528, 1984 -- 1986; MS247.001.001.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Tufts: Sackler School Drug 10th Anniv at USDA, 1986-05-28T00:00:00+00:00; MS247.001.001.00003.00001 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      860528-A to 860528 F
      Sackler School of Graduate Biomedical Sciences
    - Vet School Foster / Sculpture, 1986-05-10T00:00:00+00:00; MS247.001.001.00003.00002 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      860510-A to 860510-F
    - Employee Recognition Luncheon, 1986-05-08T00:00:00+00:00; MS247.001.001.00003.00003 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      860508-A to 860508-E
    - Tufts Medical Reunion, 1986-05-03T00:00:00+00:00; MS247.001.001.00003.00004 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      860503-A to 860503-J
      Mary Ellen McGurty
    - Tufts Chem and Engrs, 1986-04-26T00:00:00+00:00; MS247.001.001.00003.00005 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      860426-A to 860426-E
      School of Engineering
    - Peking and Mystics, 1986-04-25T00:00:00+00:00; MS247.001.001.00003.00006 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      860425
    - Tufts: Sackler Solo, 1986-04-07; MS247.001.001.00003.00007 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      860407-A to 860407-E
    - Tuftonia's Day, 1986-04-19; MS247.001.001.00003.00008 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      860419-A to 860419-D
    - 860412-A to 860412-N, 1986-04-12; MS247.001.001.00003.00009 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      860412-A to 860412-N
    - Tufts, 1986-04-01; MS247.001.001.00003.00010 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      860401-A to 860401-B
    - Tufts, 1986-03-13; MS247.001.001.00003.00011 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      860313-A to 860313-B
    - Tufts Solo Career Night, 1986-03-04; MS247.001.001.00003.00012 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      860304
    - 860220-A Color to 860220-Z color, 1986-02-20; MS247.001.001.00003.00013 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      860220-A Color to 860220-Z color
    - 860220-AA B & W to 860220-GG, 1986-02-20; MS247.001.001.00003.00014 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      860220-AA B & W to 860220-GG
    - Tufts Vet Valentine Party at Grafton, 1986-02-13; MS247.001.001.00003.00015 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      860213-A to 860213-D
    - 860207A to 860207B, 1986-02-07; MS247.001.001.00003.00016 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      860207A to 860207B
      Separated Materials
      Dean Lasagna
    - Tufts Cocaine Expert / tufts Heart / Mager, 1986-02-05; MS247.001.001.00003.00017 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      860205-A to 860205-C
      Karen Dean; Dean Lasagna
    - Solo, 1986-02-03; MS247.001.001.00003.00018 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      860203
    - Tufts Vet: Dean Loew, 1986-01-25; MS247.001.001.00003.00019 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      860125
    - Engineering Rehab 2nd Batch Canton, 1986-01-24; MS247.001.001.00003.00020 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      860124-A to 860124-D
    - Electro Optics, 1986-01-23; MS247.001.001.00003.00021 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      860123-C to 860123-G
      Bob Gonsalves; Karen
    - Parker House, 1986-01-23; MS247.001.001.00003.00022 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      860123-A to 860123-B
      Sally Helms
    - Engineering Rehab 1st Batch Boston, 1986-01-21; MS247.001.001.00003.00023 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      860121-A to 860121-E
    - Mayer Portrait, 1985-12-26; MS247.001.001.00003.00024 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      851226-A to 851226-B
    - 851219-A to 851219-D, 1985-12-19; MS247.001.001.00003.00025 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      851219-A to 851219-D
    - Tufts Dr Coffin solo, 1985-12-13; MS247.001.001.00003.00026 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      851213
    - 11A, 1985-12-03; MS247.001.001.00003.00027 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      851203-A to 851203-D
    - Tufts butterflies, 1985-11-08; MS247.001.001.00003.00028 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      851108-A to 851108-B
      Kevin Schack
    - Mayer 10th Anniversary Trustees Dinner, 1985-11-08; MS247.001.001.00003.00029 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      851108 color
    - Tufts Club, 1985-10-31; MS247.001.001.00003.00030 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      851031-A to 851031-D
    - Tufts, 1985-10-26; MS247.001.001.00003.00031 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      851026-A to 851026-F
    - Tufts 1-18 19-39, 1985-10-11; MS247.001.001.00003.00032 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      851011-A to 851011-B
    - Tufts Hockey, 1985-10-11; MS247.001.001.00003.00033 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 851026-G to 851026-O, 1985-10-26; MS247.001.001.00003.00034 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      851026-G to 851026-O
    - 851027, 1985-10-27; MS247.001.001.00003.00035 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      851027
    - Tufts, 1985-10-20; MS247.001.001.00003.00036 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      851020A to 851020D
    - 851019A to 851019D, 1985-10-19; MS247.001.001.00003.00037 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      851019A to 851019D
    - 851005A to 851005G, 1985-10-05; MS247.001.001.00003.00038 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      851005A to 851005G
    - School of Nutrition, 1985-08-05; MS247.001.001.00003.00039 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      850805-A to 850805-E
    - Tufts Mgt & Comm Dev, 1985-06-25; MS247.001.001.00003.00040 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      850625-A to 850625-E
    - Tufts Conferences, 1985-06-08; MS247.001.001.00003.00041 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      850608A to 850608G
      Marge Farley
    - Mgt & Community Dev, 1985-06-06; MS247.001.001.00003.00042 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      850606-A to 850606-C
    - Marriott Longwharf Gala, 1985-04-13; MS247.001.001.00003.00043 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      850413-A to 850413-N
    - Lowe w/Lamb, 1985-03-19; MS247.001.001.00003.00044 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      850319-A to 850319-E
    - President's Ball Solo, 1985-03-16; MS247.001.001.00003.00045 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      850316
    - 840215-A to 840215-C, 1984-02-15; MS247.001.001.00003.00046 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      840215-A to 840215-C
    - 84/85 Homecoming, 1984-10-20; MS247.001.001.00003.00047 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      841020-A to 841020-J
    - 840708-P to 840708-A, 1984-07-08; MS247.001.001.00003.00048 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      840708-P to 840708-A
    - 840521-A to 840521-L, 1984-05-21; MS247.001.001.00003.00049 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      840521-A to 840521-L
    - 840429-A to 840429-L, 1984-04-29; MS247.001.001.00003.00050 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      840429-A to 840429-L
    - Degree Ceremony, 1984 -- 1986; MS247.001.001.00003.00051 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      1 (2 sheets)
    - 840410-A to 840410-K, 1984-04-10; MS247.001.001.00003.00052 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      840410-A to 840410-K
    - Tufts Nut, 1984-03-22; MS247.001.001.00003.00053 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      840322
    - 840301-A to 840301-C, 1984-03-01; MS247.001.001.00003.00054 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      840301-A to 840301-C
    - Tufts Doctors at Hillcrest Solo, 1984-02-03; MS247.001.001.00003.00055 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      840203-A
    - 840201-A to 840201-B, 1984-02-01; MS247.001.001.00003.00056 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      840201-A to 840201-B
    - Tufts Admissions, 1984-01-02; MS247.001.001.00003.00057 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      840102-J to 840102-A
  - Tufts Volume 2 860517 to 870517, 1986 -- 1987; MS247.001.001.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Tufts Nutrition Portraits, 1987-04-24; MS247.001.001.00004.00001 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      870424-A to 870424-E
      Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy
    - Tufts Nutrition Portraits, 1987-02-27; MS247.001.001.00004.00002 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      870227-A, 870227-V
    - Tufts Commencement See also "Fletcher Grad", 1987-05-17; MS247.001.001.00004.00003 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      870517-V to 870517-Z
    - Tufts Alum Day, 1987-05-16; MS247.001.001.00004.00004 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      870516-A to 870516-AA
    - Tufts: Sackler School, 1987-05-08; MS247.001.001.00004.00005 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      870508-A to 870508-E
      Sackler School of Graduate Biomedical Sciences; Peggy Newell
    - Tufts Knip Library, 1987-05-05; MS247.001.001.00004.00006 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      870505-A to 870505-B
    - Track Coach King, 1987-05-05; MS247.001.001.00004.00007 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      870505-C to 870505-E
      Branwen Smith King
    - Tufts Development, 1987-05-03; MS247.001.001.00004.00008 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      870503-A to 870503-C
      Dr Max Tennis
    - Dental Reunion, 1987-04-25; MS247.001.001.00004.00009 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      870425-A to 870425-P
      School of Dental Medicine; Lois Shir
    - Margolis Lab Dedication Tufts Dental, 1987-04-24; MS247.001.001.00004.00010 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      870424-A to 870424-C
    - Tufts Employee Recognition Luncheon, 1987-04-22; MS247.001.001.00004.00011 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      870422-A to 870422-H
    - Tufts Secretary solo, 1987-04-09; MS247.001.001.00004.00012 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      870409
    - Tufts / Dukakis, 1987-04-09; MS247.001.001.00004.00013 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      870409-A to 870409-F
    - Tufts & Lowell Designfest Competition, 1987-04-04; MS247.001.001.00004.00014 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      870404-A to 870404-I
    - 870330-AA to 870330-OO, 1987-03-30; MS247.001.001.00004.00015 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      870330-AA to 870330-OO
    - Tufts Nutrition Portraits, 1987-02-27; MS247.001.001.00004.00016 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      870227-A to 870227-U
    - Tufts Dental Bates Day, 1987-03-04; MS247.001.001.00004.00017 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      870304-A to 870304-D
      School of Dental Medicine; Gregg Chadwick
    - Bray lab Rededication with Gov. Sununu, 1987-03-02; MS247.001.001.00004.00018 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      870302-A to 870302-D
    - MacFarlane /CDC Nutrition Chair, 1987-02-28; MS247.001.001.00004.00019 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      870228A to 870228-D
    - Tufts Murnane at Tufts Club, 1987-02-12; MS247.001.001.00004.00020 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      870212-A to 870212-E
      Don Capone
    - Tufts CURRK Software, 1987-02-18; MS247.001.001.00004.00021 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      870218-A to 870218-D
      Steve Bagney
    - 3 presidential exploration award winners, 1987-02-03; MS247.001.001.00004.00022 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      870203-A to 870203-C
      Fred Nelson ( Dean Engineering)
    - Tufts Policeman's Ball, 1987-01-31; MS247.001.001.00004.00023 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      870131-A to 870131-E
    - Signing Ceremony Somerville Mayor's Office solo, 1987-01-29; MS247.001.001.00004.00024 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      870129
    - 870127, 1987-01-27; MS247.001.001.00004.00025 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      870127
    - Tufts China Exch., 1987-01-19; MS247.001.001.00004.00026 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      870119-A to 870119-F
    - Tufts Club Valerie Kaka, 1987-01-16; MS247.001.001.00004.00027 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      870116-A to 870116-C
      Valerie Kaka
    - Tufts using Somerville Cable TV, 1986-01-22; MS247.001.001.00004.00028 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      860122-A to 860122-D
    - 870112-A to 870112-B, 1987-01-12; MS247.001.001.00004.00029 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      870112-A to 870112-B
    - Tufts Vet at the Ritz w/Myopia Hunt Club, 1986-12-11; MS247.001.001.00004.00030 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      861211-A to 861211-J
      Rob Hollister
      contact sheets
    - Ctr for Public Service also United Way, 1987-01-12; MS247.001.001.00004.00031 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      870112-C to 870112-H
      Patricia Watson; Rob Hollister
    - Tufts Vet, 1986-12-11; MS247.001.001.00004.00032 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 861216-A to 861216-B, 1986-12-16; MS247.001.001.00004.00033 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      861216-A to 861216-B
    - Mayer's Nuclear Disarm Curriculum News Conf., 1986-12-16; MS247.001.001.00004.00034 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      861216-C to 861216-D
    - Tufts: Drug Study / Post Graduate Course, 1986-11-17; MS247.001.001.00004.00035 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      861117-A to 861117-B
    - Drug Study Cont., 1986-11-20; MS247.001.001.00004.00036 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      861120 W to 861120-Z
    - 861107 B to 861107-A, 1986-11-07; MS247.001.001.00004.00037 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      861107 B to 861107-A
      Erika Ketelhohn
    - Mayer Man of Vision for the Nat'l Assn, to Prevent Blindness, 1986-11-02; MS247.001.001.00004.00038 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      861102
    - Catering Opening at Sackler, 1986-10-31; MS247.001.001.00004.00039 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      861031-A to 861031-B
      Sackler School of Graduate Biomedical Sciences: Annette Allison
    - Kennedy at McPhie, 1986-10-31; MS247.001.001.00004.00040 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      861031 A#3,4, B C
    - 1986 Homecoming, 1986-10-18; MS247.001.001.00004.00041 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      861018-A to 861018-M
    - School of Nutrition, Baby weighing, 1986-10-08; MS247.001.001.00004.00042 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      861008-A to 861008-B
      Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy; Susan Kropoweusky
    - Rebecca Flewelling visitors to South Africa w/Boston skyline, 1986-09-26; MS247.001.001.00004.00043 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      860926
    - Tufts: Murrow Center 3rd world journalists, 1986-09-16; MS247.001.001.00004.00044 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      860916-A to 860916-D
    - B/W from second session Vet Sch Horse poster, 1986-09-08; MS247.001.001.00004.00045 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      860908-N to 860908-W
    - solo, 1986-08-07; MS247.001.001.00004.00046 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      860807
    - 860806A to 860806P, 1986-08-06; MS247.001.001.00004.00047 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      860806A to 860806P
    - Tufts Paiste /Mulhu, 1986-08-01; MS247.001.001.00004.00048 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      860801
    - Tufts Summer School, 1986-07-24; MS247.001.001.00004.00049 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      860724-A to 860724-J
    - Bray Lab & Dean, 1986-07-09; MS247.001.001.00004.00050 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      860709-A to 860709-B
    - Tufts Solo, 1986-06-30; MS247.001.001.00004.00051 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      860630
    - Tufts Solo, 1986-06-29; MS247.001.001.00004.00052 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      860629
    - Fred Nickless Retire, 1986-06-22; MS247.001.001.00004.00053 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      860622-A to 860622-F